# ANTON KOVAL

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT
+48 721-806-686
toniokovalski@gmail.com
github.com/Toniokovalski
Mrągowo, 11-700 Poland
SKILLS
<ul> <li>Vue/Vuex;</li> <li>React/Redux;</li> <li>JS5/JS6+/jQuerry;</li> <li>Less/Sass/CSS3;</li> <li>HTML5;</li> <li>Responsive PSD to HTML;</li> <li>Webpack/Gulp/Grunt/Bower;</li> <li>Git;</li> <li>Photoshop/Figma/Creative cloud;</li> <li>Bootstrap;</li> <li>PHP (basic) / Twig;</li> <li>Ruby (basic) / Slim;</li> <li>Java (basic)</li> <li>Wordpress;</li> </ul>
EDUCATION
Bachelor of Economics
Kyiv National Economic University
Kyiv, Ukraine 2003-2008
Bachelor of advocacy
Ukraine Academy of Advocacy
Kyiv, Ukraine 2009-2012
LANGUAGES
Ukrainian —————————————————————————————————
English
Polish
Russian

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced in front-end and offering skills in JavaScript, React and VueJS. Advanced skill in English and accustomed to working with cross-cultural, global teams.

7+ years in web development and games development. Familiar with JS frameworks. Close work with the Back-end developers. At the moment working in international company as a software engineer using React/ES6+JS.

In total have more than 20 year of commercial experience.

## WORK HISTORY

# **Software Engineer**

GE HealthCare

July 2022 - June 2023

- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript (React) to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms
- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance requirements
- · Contributed to projects within Scrum project management environments
- Worked with project managers, developers, quality assurance and customers to resolve technical issues
- Promoted technical leadership to entry-level and junior engineers in complex enterprise system environment
- Checked client code for bugs and weaknesses using approved troubleshooting methods
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality
- Integrated third-party tools and components into applications

# Sinior Front-End Developer (React/VueJS)

Xyrality GmbH

December 2019 - May 2022

- · Creating browser games and webviews for devices and support existing ones
- Building new app using new technologies like Vue/React and ES6+
- Support old game with huge legacy that exist 10+ using ES5 and React
- Adding new functionalities to projects
- Work with close collaboration with back-end developers and designers

### Front-End Developer (React)

 $\label{thm:digital classified similar} \mbox{Digital classifieds.in.ua})$ 

July 2018 - December 2019

- Working with international digital projects
- · Building new pages and functions according to markups
- · Support old version using ES5/JQuery
- Build new app using React/ES6+ bug fixing
- Skilled at working independently and collaboratively in a team environment

## Front-End Developer

Evoplay

June 2017 - July 2018

- Working with big gambling projects
- Building new pages and functions according to markups
- Coding from scratch and bug fixing
- Tested web-based product functionality and delivered iterations to customer.

## **Junior Front-End Developer**

Everad

October 2016 - June 2017

- Coded using HTML, CSS and JavaScript to develop features for both mobile and desktop platforms.
- Produced websites compatible with multiple browsers.
- Coding from scratch and bug fixing
- Email/Landing-page coding